Seino!
GOROGORO CHANNEL GO!
Yes, that's right, today's
Machibura in
Shimokitazawa!
Yay!
Today
Yes, I'm here!
I'd like to try some food stores...
Various things.
I'd like to find a place to eat.
I'd like to look for them as I walk.
I'm hungry.
Just in time.
It's lunch time.
I've done a lot of research, haven't I?
Looks delicious.
Hey, Mi. Do you come to Shimokita?
I've only been a couple of times.
You know what?
And I've only been once.
I come here for vintage clothes, so I've probably never eaten there.
But I have an image of vintage clothes.
Oh, your clothes are so cute.
Wow, they're on sale. I've never seen anything like it.
I know this place.
Cute. West Coast.
But it smells so good.
Isn't that it?
Oh, it's really here!
I'm already hungry.
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Let's go, let's go!
Isn't this amazing? Oh, no.
I want this.
Hand it over.
Active1 amongst ska agriculture.
Iture scary me4
Gande Kerry
interrupted
I'm going to see Farmer Ferry Caller
2 umm
Shunde Alsader f 1 Roma
Kerry is the second time
I made a mistake.
I don't know about the second one.
I got it.
The size speaks for itself.
Yeah, same.
Wow.
Isn't it dangerous?
Oh, my God.
Did you see that?
I got it on my hand.
Bon appétit.
This one's more beautiful.
It's good, isn't it?
Bon appétit.
It tastes like mustard.
Mmmm!
I want to buy something for the members.
I'm so confused.
Everyone always buys me something.
Some kind of waffle?
Meat rolls?
No, no, no, no, no.
Sponge cake?
Sponge cake.
What do the members want?
What's easier to eat?
I think the easiest to eat is sponge cake.
Do you want some sponge cake?
Do you want to buy some sponge cake? For everyone.
What? Marshmallow game?
Marshmallow game?
What world is Mario in?
Kahohli-poing.
Mohler.
Mazariwamaya forfeiting the day's food to something else.
After that, we'll have dessert.
They go so well together!
Looks so good!
Would you like to propose a toast?
Yes. Yes.
Yes, ma'am.
Make sure it's still in your ass.
Bon appétit.
It's good.
It's sweet, but it tastes like coffee.
I was wondering if I could nibble on a lemon.
Lemons are slippery?
Really?
It smells so lemony.
We did that thing once where we both had to eat a lemon with a facial expression.
We had a showdown once.
I miss it.
It sounded great.
Summer was fun.
We went to Okinawa.
We released a lot of stuff.
I don't know, MDH has a lot of summer events.
That's true.
It's getting more and more exciting.
Oh yeah, when the date comes up, you'll do it?
Well, we're going to do it.
You get to eat really good food.
I see.
I'm really going to be with you guys every day.
Every day?
I'm going to wait a lot.
Everyone keeps a calendar, right?
Yeah.
Like, what's happening on that day.
You know, like, what's happening on that day.
Seriously, for real, for real.
I'm really with you guys every day.
I'll see you tomorrow.
And the day after tomorrow, and the day after tomorrow.
We'll be together all the time.
Yeah.
We'll be together more than family.
Yeah. - Yeah.
Definitely.
Thank you for dinner.
Thank you for the food.
It was delicious.
I'm very satisfied.
Very satisfying!
Lots of interesting ingredients
Yeah.
It's cute.
It's great.
That's great.
Don't do that.
MV...
I thought it was a music video or something.
Oh, my God.
And the hat is cute.
The hat is so cute.
It's so cute.
Now I want to buy souvenirs for everyone!
One marshmallow, two marshmallows
One more time, please.
1 marshmallow, 2 marshmallows
2 marshmallows, 3 marshmallows
4 marshmallows
Oh, here it comes.
They're here.
Me?
You're going to see a lot of Minami today, aren't you?
So I bought souvenirs for the members.
Yay!
We can put chocolate on ourselves, too!
Chocolate fondue sponge cake?
Cheers!
Ta-da!
Sorry. Bon appétit.
Mmm!
Mmmmmm!
The sponge cake feels so strange!
Yuck! Ne!
Sssshhhh! Swish! Ssshhhh! Like that.
Maybe this is it.
That's it!
Thank you for the food!
Shimokitazawa as a landscape
Hey!
I got to go to so many places.
I think I got to go to a lot of places I wanted to go today!
It was fun!
It was a lot of fun!
Let's come visit again!
Let's go!
Thank you for watching!
Thank you very much!
If you liked this video, please subscribe to the channel, rate it highly, and comment!
Bye bye!